http://www.learning4liferesources.com/privacy-policy.html

Career & Academic Coaching
Hollandcodes.com since 1995
Menu
HomeMBTI - Sale!
Career Tests By Age or TypeAdultsBlack Lives MatterExplore Majors/ CareersKids/ Children TestsOnline TestsPrinted TestsPrinted Worksheets
More InformationAbout UsContact UsGoogle SearchHolland CodesMeditationPrivacy PoliciesSite MapPurchase Orders$5 or lessNew Store!
Privacy Policies and Guarantees
Holland Codes Resource Center Privacy Notice
Privacy Noticerevised 5/22/18This
is the privacy notice of Holland Codes Resource Center. In this document,
"we", "our", or "us" refer to Holland Codes
Resource Center.
We
are Federal ID #:  86-0943276 registered
in USA.
Our
registered office is at 4133 E. Siesta Lane, Phoenix, AZ 85050.
Introduction
1.
This is a notice to inform you of our policy about all information that
we record about you. It sets out the conditions under which we may process any
information that we collect from you, or that you provide to us. It covers
information that could identify you (“personal information”) and information
that could not. In the context of the law and this notice, “process” means
collect, store, transfer, use or otherwise act on information.
2.
We regret that if there are one or more points below with which you are
not happy, your only recourse is to leave our website immediately.
3.
We take seriously the protection of your privacy and confidentiality. We
understand that all visitors to our website are entitled to know that their
personal data will not be used for any purpose unintended by them, and will not
accidentally fall into the hands of a third party.
4.
We undertake to preserve the confidentiality of all information you
provide to us, and hope that you reciprocate.
5.
Our policy complies with UK law accordingly implemented, including that
required by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
6.
The law requires us to tell you about your rights and our obligations to
you in regards to the processing and control of your personal data. We do this
now, by requesting that you read the information provided at www.knowyourprivacyrights.org
7.
Except as set out below, we do not share, or sell, or disclose to a
third party, any information collected through our website.
The bases on
which we process information about you
The law
requires us to determine under which of six defined bases we process different
categories of your personal information, and to notify you of the basis for
each category.
If a basis on which we process your personal information is no longer
relevant then we shall immediately stop processing your data.
If the basis changes then if required by law we shall notify you of the
change and of any new basis under which we have determined that we can continue
to process your information.
1.
Information we process because we have a contractual obligation with you
When you create an account on our website, buy a product or service from
us, or otherwise agree to our terms and conditions, a contract is formed
between you and us.
In order to carry out our obligations under that contract we must
process the information you give us. Some of this information may be personal
information.
We may use it in order to:
1.1.
verify your identity for security purposes
1.2.
sell products to you
1.3.
provide you with our services
1.4.
provide you with suggestions and advice on products, services and how to
obtain the most from using our website
We process this information on the basis there is a contract between us,
or that you have requested we use the information before we enter into a legal
contract.
Additionally, we may aggregate this information in a general way and use
it to provide class information, for example to monitor our performance with
respect to a particular service we provide. If we use it for this purpose, you
as an individual will not be personally identifiable.
We shall continue to process this information until the contract between
us ends or is terminated by either party under the terms of the contract.
2.
Information we process with your consent
Through certain actions when otherwise there is no contractual
relationship between us, such as when you browse our website or ask us to
provide you more information about our business, including our products and
services, you provide your consent to us to process information that may be
personal information.
Wherever possible, we aim to obtain your explicit consent to process
this information, for example, by asking you to agree to our use of cookies.
Sometimes you might give your consent implicitly, such as when you send
us a message by e-mail to which you would reasonably expect us to reply.
Except where you have consented to our use of your information for a
specific purpose, we do not use your information in any way that would identify
you personally. We may aggregate it in a general way and use it to provide
class information, for example to monitor the performance of a particular page
on our website.
If you have given us explicit permission to do so, we may from time to
time pass your name and contact information to selected associates whom we
consider may provide services or products you would find useful.
We continue to process your information on this basis until you withdraw
your consent or it can be reasonably assumed that your consent no longer
exists.
You may withdraw your consent at any time by instructing us cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com.
However, if you do so, you may not be able to use our website or our services
further.
3.
Information we process for the purposes of legitimate interests
We may process information on the basis there is a legitimate interest,
either to you or to us, of doing so.
Where we process your information on this basis, we do after having
given careful consideration to:
·
whether the same objective could be achieved through other means
·
whether processing (or not processing) might cause you harm
·
whether you would expect us to process your data, and whether you would,
in the round, consider it reasonable to do so
For example, we may process your data on this basis for the purposes of:
·
record-keeping for the proper and necessary administration of the Holland Codes Resource Center.
·
responding to unsolicited communication from you to which we believe you
would expect a response
·
protecting and asserting the legal rights of any party
·
insuring against or obtaining professional advice that is required to
manage Holland Codes Resource Center’s
risk
·
protecting your interests where we believe we have a duty to do so
4.
Information we process because we have a legal obligation
We are subject to the law like everyone else. Sometimes, we must process
your information in order to comply with a statutory obligation.
For example, we may be required to give information to legal authorities
if they so request or if they have the proper authorization such as a search
warrant or court order.
This may include your personal information.
Specific uses of
information you provide to us
5.
Information provided on the understanding that it will be shared with a
third party
Our website allows you to post information with a view to that
information being read, copied, downloaded, or used by other people.
Examples include:
5.1.
posting a message our forum
5.2.
tagging an image
5.3.
clicking on an icon next to another visitor’s message to convey your
agreement, disagreement or thanks
In posting personal information, it is up to you to satisfy yourself
about the privacy level of every person who might use it.
We
do not specifically use this information except to allow it to be displayed or
shared.
We do store it, and we reserve a right to use it in the future in any
way we decide.
Once your information enters the public domain, we have no control over
what any individual third party may do with it. We accept no responsibility for
their actions at any time.
Provided your request is reasonable and there is no legal basis for us
to retain it, then at our discretion we may agree to your request to delete
personal information that you have posted. You can make a request by contacting
us at cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com
6.
Complaints regarding content on our website
Our
website is a publishing medium. Anyone may register and then publish
information about himself, herself or some other person.
We
do not moderate or control what is posted.
If you complain about any of the content on our website, we shall
investigate your complaint.
If we feel it is justified or if we believe the law requires us to do
so, we shall remove the content while we investigate.
Free speech is a fundamental right, so we have to make a judgment as to
whose right will be obstructed: yours, or that of the person who posted the
content that offends you.
If we think your complaint is vexatious or without any basis, we shall
not correspond with you about it.
7.
Information relating to your method of payment
Payment information is never taken by us or transferred
to us either through our website or otherwise. Our employees and contractors
never have access to it.
At the point of payment, you are transferred to a secure
page on the website of PayPal or some other reputable payment service provider.
That page may be branded to look like a page on our website, but it is not
controlled by us.
8.
Information about your direct debit
When you agree to set up a direct debit arrangement, the information you
give to us is passed to Paypal for processing according to our instructions. We
do not keep a copy.
We keep this information only for the duration of the direct debit
arrangement.
We are registered under the direct debit guarantee scheme. This provides
for the customer's bank to refund disputed payments without question, pending
further investigation. Direct debits can only be set up for payments to
beneficiaries that are approved originators of direct debits. In order to be
approved, these beneficiaries are subjected to careful vetting procedures. Once
approved, they are required to give indemnity guarantees through their banks.
9.
Sending a message to our support team
When you contact us, whether by telephone, through our website or by e-mail,
we collect the data you have given to us in order to reply with the information
you need.
We record your request and our reply in order to increase the efficiency
of Holland Codes Resource Center.
We
keep personally identifiable information associated with your message, such as
your name and email address so as to be able to track our communications with
you to provide a high quality service.
10.
Complaining
When we receive a complaint, we record all the information you have
given to us.
We use that information to resolve your complaint.
If
your complaint reasonably requires us to contact some other person, we may
decide to give to that other person some of the information contained in your
complaint. We do this as infrequently as possible, but it is a matter for our
sole discretion as to whether we do give information, and if we do, what that
information is.
We may also compile statistics showing information obtained from this
source to assess the level of service we provide, but not in a way that could
identify you or any other person.
11.
Affiliate and business partner information
This is information given to us by you in your capacity as an affiliate
of us or as a business partner.
It allows us to recognize visitors that you have referred to us, and to
credit to you commission due for such referrals. It also includes information
that allows us to transfer commission to you.
The information is not used for any other purpose.
We undertake to preserve the confidentiality of the information and of
the terms of our relationship.
We expect any affiliate or partner to agree to reciprocate this policy.
Use of
information we collect through automated systems when you visit our website12.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard
drive by your web browser when you visit any website. They allow information
gathered on one web page to be stored until it is needed for use on another,
allowing a website to provide you with a personalized experience and the
website owner with statistics about how you use the website so that it can be
improved.
Some cookies may last for a defined period of time, such as one day or
until you close your browser. Others last indefinitely.
Your web browser should allow you to delete any you choose. It also
should allow you to prevent or limit their use.
Our website does not use cookies.
13.
Personal identifiers from your browsing activity
Requests by your web browser to our servers for web pages and other
content on our website are recorded.
We record information such as your geographical location, your Internet
service provider and your IP address. We also record information about the
software you are using to browse our website, such as the type of computer or
device and the screen resolution.
We use this information in aggregate to assess the popularity of the
webpages on our website and how we perform in providing content to you.
If combined with other information we know about you from previous
visits, the data possibly could be used to identify you personally, even if you
are not signed in to our website.
14.
Our use of re-marketing
Re-marketing involves placing a cookie on your computer when you browse
our website in order to be able to serve to you an advert for our products or
services when you visit some other website.
We may use a third party to provide us with re-marketing services from
time to time. If so, then if you have consented to our use of cookies, you may
see advertisements for our products and services on other websites.
Disclosure and
sharing of your information15.
Information we obtain from third parties
Although we do not disclose your personal information to any third party
(except as set out in this notice), we sometimes receive data that is
indirectly made up from your personal information from third parties whose
services we use.
No
such information is personally identifiable to you.
16.
Third party advertising on our website
Third parties may advertise on our website. In doing so, those parties,
their agents or other companies working for them may use technology that
automatically collects information about you when their advertisement is
displayed on our website.
They may also use other technology such as cookies or JavaScript to
personalize the content of, and to measure the performance of their adverts.
We do not have control over these technologies or the data that these
parties obtain. Accordingly, this privacy notice does not cover the information
practices of these third parties.
17.
Credit reference
To assist in combating fraud, we share information with credit reference
agencies, so far as it relates to clients or customers who instruct their
credit card issuer to cancel payment to us without having first provided an
acceptable reason to us and given us the opportunity to refund their money.
18.
Data may be processed in the USA and Canada
Our websites are hosted in USA and Canada .
We may also use outsourced services in countries outside the USA from time to time in other aspects of our business.
Accordingly data obtained within the USA or any other country could be
processed outside the USA.
For
example, some of the software our website uses may have been developed in the
United States of America or in Canada.
We use the following safeguards with respect to data transferred outside
the USA:
18.1.     the processor is within the same corporate
group as our business or organization and abides by the same binding corporate
rules regarding data processing.
18.2.     the data protection clauses in our contracts
with data processors include transfer clauses written by or approved by a
18.5.     both our organization and the processor are
public authorities between whom there is either a legally binding agreement or
administrative arrangements approved by a supervisory authority in the European
Union relating to protection of your information
Access to your
own information19.
Access to your personal information
19.1.     At any time you may review
or update personally identifiable information that we hold about you, by
signing in to your account on our website.
19.2.     To obtain a copy of any
information that is not provided on our website you may send us a request at cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com.
19.3.     After receiving the
request, we will tell you when we expect to provide you with the information,
and whether we require any fee for providing it to you.
20.
Removal of your information
If you wish us to remove personally identifiable information from our
website, you may contact us at cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com.
This may limit the service we can provide to you.
21.
Verification of your information
When we receive any request to access, edit or delete personal
identifiable information we shall first take reasonable steps to verify your
identity before granting you access or otherwise taking any action. This is
important to safeguard your information.
Other matters22.
Use of site by children
22.1.     We do not sell products or
provide services for purchase by children, nor do we market to children.
22.2.     If you are under 18, you
may use our website only with consent from a parent or guardian
23.
Encryption of data sent between us
We
use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) certificates to verify our identity to your
browser and to encrypt any data you give us.
Whenever
information is transferred between us, you can check that it is done so using
SSL by looking for a closed padlock symbol or other trust mark in your
browser’s URL bar or toolbar.
24.
How you can complain
24.1.     If you are not happy with
our privacy policy or if have any complaint then you should tell us by email.
Our email address is cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com
24.2.     If a dispute is not settled
then we hope you will agree to attempt to resolve it by engaging in good faith
with us in a process of mediation or arbitration.
24.3.     If you are in any way
dissatisfied about how we process your personal information, you have a right
to lodge a complaint
25.
Retention period for personal data
Except as otherwise mentioned in this privacy notice, we keep your
personal information only for as long as required by us:
25.1.     to provide you with the
services you have requested;
25.2.     to comply with other law,
including for the period demanded by our tax authorities;
25.3.     to support a claim or
defense in court.
26.
Compliance with the law
Our privacy policy has been compiled so as to comply with the law of
every country or legal jurisdiction in which we aim to do business. If you
think it fails to satisfy the law of your jurisdiction, we should like to hear
from you.
However, ultimately it is your choice as to whether you wish to use our
website.
27.
Review of this privacy policy
We may update this privacy notice from time to time as necessary. The
terms that apply to you are those posted here on our website on the day you use
our website. We advise you to print a copy for your records.
If you have any question regarding our privacy
policy, please contact us. at cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com
Guarantees, Shipping & Return Policies
We guarantee all our products to be brand new and fully as described. We ship no blemishes, seconds, or any inferior variations.
We also guarantee that your shopping experience will be a secure and enjoyable one. If your shopping experience is substandard in any way, please contact us through this Contact Form...
We can be reached through email below.
E-mail: Send questions about Holland Code information, assessment, and customer support questions to e-mail us at cs.hollandcodes@gmail.com.
Shipping Policy
All of our products are shipped within 1-2 business days. Should a product be out of stock, we'll notify you of the delay immediately. If that happens (not likely), we will ask if you prefer to cancel your order.
Return Policy for Printed Assessments and Books
We stand behind every product we sell. If you are not satisfied, simply return the item to us within 30 days via insured parcel post or UPS.
Returned products must be in like-new, unused condition with original packaging and materials. A receipt must accompany all returns. Please add a note stating the reason for the return.
Please send the return to us at -
Holland Codes Resource Center
Returns
4133 E. Siesta Lane
Phoenix, AZ 85050
We will be happy to make an exchange or refund the purchase price.
A 10% re-stocking fee will be applied towards your refund.
Please note: The Return Policy does not apply to Online Assessments (Make a Career Profile or Career Explorers Guidance System) or to Downloads (Holland Code Tool Kit).
This Form cannot be submitted until the missing fields (labelled below in red) have been filled in
Get more information.
Please note that all fields followed by an asterisk must be filled in.
First Name*
Last Name*
E-Mail Address*
Web Site URL
Street Address
City*
State/Prov*
Zip/Postal Code
Country*CountryUnited StatesCanada----------------AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntiguaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEast TimorEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGrenadaGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsraelItalyIvory CoastJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribadiNorth KoreaSouth KoreaKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoFederated States of MicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMontenegroMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaS. Georgia and S. Sandwich Isls.Saint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSt. HelenaSt. Pierre and MiquelonSudanSurinameSvalbardSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluU.S. Minor Outlying IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamUS Virgin IslandsWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenYugoslavia (former)ZaireZambiaZimbabwe
Home Phone*
Business Phone
Fax
Get additional information or enter comments.*
Please enter the word that you see below.
Get motivated and inspired! Text/ call us at (602) 753-9112 (12pm to 5pm GMT-07:00) or moreinfo@hollandcodes.com.
4133 E. Siesta Ln. Phoenix, AZ 85050, Copyright © 2004-2017 Dr. Mary Askew.
All Rights Reserved.
